The hunters who came to investigate the
anomalies surrounding the White Wolf's Den
learned that a branch of the mage association
Akashic Tower was behind it—
specifically, a group lead
by Noctus Cochlear.
Mages, supporting fire!
The culmination of our research: "Akasha."
The ultimate weapon that
will destroy you all.
Gark!
We're getting nowhere fast like this!
We need to get out there, too!
No.
There are non-combatants here as well!
If we overextend ourselves,
we'll suffer casualties.
Damn it!
He's fast.
Sven!
I'm fine!
Keep the pressure on them!
If we could take down just one...
This is awesome!
Krai, I'm falling in love again.
Liz?!
Stifled Shadow?
Sis?!
I see.
Guys, reinforcements from
the Master have arrived!
Let's go crush them!
We are now in the golden age
of the treasure hunters!
Amid the sparkling talent on
display in the capital of Zebrudia,
there was one man who stood
out amongst all others!
His name is Krai Andrey.
This is an epic tale
full of glory and agony,
of how he became renowned
for being the leader
of the strongest party he founded
with his childhood friends,
and also the master of the strongest clan!
This is my partner in crime, Hail's Tusk!
Anybody who wants to be
encased in ice, come at me!
Episode 09
I Want to Teach Love and Peace
"I Want to Teach Love and Peace."
Let This Grieving Soul Retire
I guess she took off...
I guess she did.
Liz is supposed to be my bodyguard.
Master.
Huh?
There's something close.
What?
There are multiple living beings nearby.
It seems they've noticed us.
Shall we capture them?
I think we can just ignore them.
Oh, are you sure?
Yes.
It's natural for animals
to be in the forest.
If anything, I feel bad for messing
up the place they call home.
Love and peace.
Well, let's go.
S-Sure.
What is the meaning of
this, Thousand Tricks?
You are well aware of our
presence, and yet...
Oh...
Is something wrong?
Uh, no.
I'll let you take it from here.
I'll follow your lead.
Yes, sir!
Your wish is my command, Master!
Just leave it to me!
Yup, yup.
No matter how well-crafted your plans are,
unexpected things will always happen.
Unwanted changes to your
strategy in the field...
Repeated insubordination
from disciples...
And then, the worst imaginable
reinforcement for the Malice Eaters.
I can't believe you're
struggling against this trash.
Si, you suck.
Sis, why are you here?
I begged Krai to let me.
Oh, wow!
That's so hard. Impressive!
I suspected those disciples would not be
able to unleash Akasha's abilities properly.
Not going to fall behind here!
This will fail to be a test
of Akasha's abilities.
Stop playing with me!
What?
That's impossible...
That huge thing?
It's basically like Ansem!
You know, they do look
around the same height.
Was he the model?
It even has ranged attacks?!
Damn it!
Sitri!
Got anything up your sleeve?
We're lucky it doesn't have
any area-of-effect attacks.
Geez!
What is this?!
Why is only coming after me?!
My sister isn't very strong against those.
I'll kill you for sure!
Her opponent is extremely durable.
Since she's specialized for speed,
she won't be able to destroy it.
We might have to go into overtime and
wait until the golem runs out of mana.
Never!
I'll pulverize it now!
Idiot!
Take that!
That worked!
What the hell did they build?!
Damn, I thought I could defeat it quickly.
Ugh! It's over!
Time's up!
Stifled Shadow. What do you mean, "over"?
What are guys doing?
Krai?
Oh. Hi, Sven! Good work.
So that's Thousand Tricks?
Sorry!
I really wanted to finish him off before
you showed up, but he's so tough!
Yep, sure looks like it.
I see.
It really is over.
Krai, run!
Master!
Huh? What is it?
Master, it's coming!
Yep, sure looks like it.
That was awesome, Krai!
What did you do?
I didn't see it at all!
Huh?
Hey, Ti!
Why are you hanging off of him?!
Sorry, it was kinda dark,
and I couldn't see very well.
Did something happen?
Huh?!
Just as I thought, the Akashic
Tower guys have escaped.
That they have.
Speaking of, what did Krai end
up doing there at the end?
Did he use a relic?
In his own words, "I think it just
flew off by itself. Like, boing."
Or something like that.
Like hell!
Well, whatever.
We confiscated their
documents and materials.
We'll leave the rest to the Institute for
Relic Research and the Knight's Order.
Thank you for the reinforcement, Krai.
They were much stronger than anticipated.
Yes, yes.
That was just Liz running off at
the perfect time, but whatever...
C'mon, do it like you mean it.
Yes, ma'am!
So, this mage association,
Something-Or-Another Tower...
Your arch-nemesis is with them?
They're called the Akashic Tower.
Yeah, that was it.
Is there anything I can do to help?
Thank you.
But...
I think I'll try to settle
the score myself first.
What?
You're telling me that Sophia has
infiltrated Thousand Tricks' clan?!
It's unmistakable.
That's definitely her.
Right.
Yes.
And have they noticed?
I do not know.
It is also possible that they are aware
and just observing her moves.
He easily saw through the anomalies
at the White Wolf's Den,
knew about the existence of our
base and still ignored it,
left this matter to his underlings
until the last moment,
and then let you escape
while laughing about it...
I simply cannot fathom
what he is thinking.
Enough.
Trying to keep up with him would be foolish.
We will leave Zebrudia at once.
Yes, sir.
If we continue our search for the truth,
I'm sure an opportunity for
a comeback will present itself.
Call Sophia back at once!
Sitri's Slime...
If I could just find that...
Enough is enough!
You set all these things into motion,
and you still want me to believe
that you don't know anything?
That's what I'm saying...
Thousand Tricks, your penchant
for secrecy is going too far.
We acknowledge your intelligence network
surpasses even our own,
despite our governmental affiliation.
But this incident
is beyond the scope
of your "Thousand Trials."
What?!
How did me being an incompetent leader
turn into official government business?
Noctus Cochlear's experiments
amount to felonies in the empire.
Therefore, as a citizen,
you are obligated to cooperate.
Do you understand?
Then you should talk to Sitri, not me.
I left this entire mission in her hands.
But...
I suppose you are hesitant to
officially summon her for questioning?
That incident three years ago...
Had it not been for Branch
Manager Gark's efforts,
Sitri would have remained falsely accused.
That incident...
The circumstantial evidence
all pointed to her.
Her demotion and the second name "Deep Black,"
branding her the worst of the worst...
We can't undo those things anymore.
South Isteria's mass prison break incident.
The vile criminals that escaped
are all still at large.
It was so ridiculous.
As if Sitri would ever be mixed
up in something like that.
Wh-What is this place?
Who are you?
Sophia.
You can drop the act now.
We're out of time.
We'll be leaving the capital immediately.
"Sophia"?
You're mistaken...
I am Talia Wydman.
Maybe she cast a spell on herself so
Thousand Tricks can't unmask her.
Or perhaps she's lost her memory.
No, wait.
It's hostile towards Sophia!
Who the hell are you?!
I told you... I'm Talia.
I have returned.
Huh?
Is that... me?
I apologize for being late.
There were a few things I had to clean up.
Why?
Why are you not at all
surprised to see a woman
who looks just like you, Sophia?
Master, that's not quite it.
She is not the one who looks like me.
I'm the one who looks like her.
And you flatter me by saying
we look exactly alike.
If you take a closer look at us, you'll see
differences that could not be erased.
My bust and height are both
slightly larger than hers.
Master, the key to a disguise...
is to fully understand prominent features,
and then replicate the gist of them.
People are often looking,
but they usually aren't seeing.
Wh-Who are you?
Sitri Smart!
How dare you?!
You turned yourself into
Sophia to come here?
Incorrect again, Master.
Do you still not understand?
I've been myself from the very beginning.
Ever since that day.
Sophia Black has always been Sitri Smart.
Wh-What are you saying?
Are you saying, you—
You planned to betray
us from the very start!
Please stop, Flick.
The reason I became a disciple is
because I was drawn by the abilities
of the Master of Mages, Noctus Cochlear.
I'm no different than any of you.
I respect our master.
For his relentlessly inquisitive mind,
his dedication, and his abilities.
He also gathered a plethora of expensive
equipment and precious materials.
I can't even fathom how much time, money,
and risk it would have taken for me to build
the agitation device or Akasha by myself...
But the jig is up.
Krai letting all of you go
was his warning to me.
"It's dangerous, so you better
call it quits and come home."
You're saying that Thousand Tricks knew
you were taking part in our research,
and deliberately—
Please don't misunderstand.
I didn't tell him anything.
But Krai is able to see through everything.
You can't hide anything from him.
Krai is a very kind person.
He set the stage while I was gone,
sending high-level hunters to give me a
chance to test the fruits of our research.
Of course, Akasha's abilities
left nothing to be desired!
But when he arrived in person, I made
it jump back by itself. Like, boing.
If the battle had continued, it would
have led to more damage and casualties.
This was enough for now.
All the results of our
research were confiscated,
and you will all be
apprehended as criminals...
But I will carry on, so please don't worry.
You're insane.
You really think the end
—the research—justifies all means?
No wonder you were a
suspect in that incident,
Deep Black!
I really hate that second name.
It's proof of my past failure.
I'm sorry I never said
anything to you, Talia.
It's something I've learned.
If I become too visible, eventually
it'll become a problem.
Your hair and eyes are pretty,
so they stand out.
That's why I figured becoming
you would be the easiest.
Sophia Black will now cease to exist,
along with the second name I hate.
Sitri Smart
Hunter level 2
Master.
From now on, you get to
be the "Worst of the Worst"...
"Worst of the Worst"
"Deep Black."
Why, you...!
What?!
Living beings won't act on logic alone.
They need love.
That is, love and peace.
What a joke!
Please listen to me, Master.
Th-This can't be.
Nobody can be completely unscathed
after being hit by my Kaiser Flame...
Sheesh!
For the last time, please listen to me!
There's a reason why
I didn't get hurt at all.
It's the result of my own research.
Contrary to the transmogrified phantoms,
this here absorbs mana
material and magic to grow.
I call it Sitri's Slime.
A slime?!
If it eats mana material
to grow, that means...
it will devour everything in this world!
Are you even aware?!
That's why I'd like to test its abilities.
I'm truly lucky till the very end.
I mean, I get to test this cutie
on mages as powerful as you.
Master! Please run!
We'll handle this!
My disciples, I leave this in your hands!
Yes, sir!
Are you sure, Flick?
Dying for someone who heavily favored
the newcomer Sophia instead of you?
Someone who hurt your pride so badly?
We're nothing like you!
No matter how he treats us, we
have nothing but respect for him!
That's right!
Exactly!
Forgive me.
I will not let your sacrifice
as my disciples be in vain...
Take that!
Kill, kill, kill!
What in the world are you?!
Kill, kill, kill.
As the weakest member of the Grievers,
I needed to get my hands on power quickly.
A golem takes a lot of time and resources.
So I figured, what about a chimera?
That's a chimera?
I wanted high-quality materials.
That prison really was ideal.
Are you saying...
I let so many of them out,
but when I gathered the usable
parts, it was only enough for one.
Kill, kill.
But it's pretty amazing, right?
I called it Killiam!
Deep Black... You...
Kill, kill, kill, kill.
The magic materials from a great
sage are hard to come by, Master.
Kill, kill, kill!
Kill, kill, kill, kill,
kill, kill, kill, kill!
So those guys from the Something-Or-Another
Tower have all lost their memories.
They confiscated chimeras and golems
and all kinds of other things.
They probably did some weird experiment
that blew up in their own faces.
I heard one of our people
got mixed up in that?
If you mean Talia, she's fine.
She's suffering from a lapse in memory,
but its nothing to worry about.
I'm glad to hear that.
It's too bad about Noctus Cochlear,
but in the end, you do need a perpetrator.
I'll get my materials next time.
Yes, yes. Sounds good.
I have no idea what she's talking about,
but I never do, so whatever.
So, the confiscated research materials
will eventually be sold off
by the Institute for Relic Research.
If possible, I'd like for us to get our hands
on the Akasha golem and the Malice Eaters.
Golem and... water?
Is she talking about a drink?
Sure, I'll negotiate.
Thank you very much.
Oh, that reminds me.
Whatever happened to that
arch-nemesis of yours?
Did you catch her?
No. She...
has gone far away and will
never show her face here again.
I used colored water.
By: Sitri and Killiam and Talia
Kill, kill, kill.
Sitri, what?!
Who is this person?!
It's Killiam!
Strong in the face of a terrifying threat,
you're too sturdy, you berserker.
Just arrived in the capital today from another land!
I see.
Next time on Let This Grieving Soul...
Episode 10
I Want to Be Renowned in the Capital
...Retire...
I want to kill, kill...
Kill, kill, kill.
"I Want to Be Renowned in the Capital."
So this is the capital, Zebrudia, eh?